Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - NC State, 1961 October 28
    - Duke vs. NC State: 3 of 3, 1961 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 100, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0422)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1961 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 100, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0423)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1961 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 100, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0424)
  - Michigan, 1961 November 04
    - Duke vs. Michigan: 1 of 3 regular, 1961 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 97, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0425)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: 2 of 3 regular, 1961 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 97, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0426)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: 3 of 3 regular, 1961 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 97, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0427)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: 1 of 3 wide, 1961 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 97, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0428)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: 2 of 3 wide, 1961 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 97, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0429)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: 3 of 3 wide, 1961 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 97, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0430)
  - Navy, 1961 November 11
    Duke win, score: 30-09
    - Duke vs. Navy: 1 of 3, 1961 November 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0431)
    - Duke vs. Navy: 2 of 3, 1961 November 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0432)
    - Duke vs. Navy: 3 of 3, 1961 November 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0433)
  - North Carolina, 1961 November 18
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 1 of 3, 1961 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 99, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0434)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 of 3, 1961 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 99, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0435)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 3 of 3, 1961 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 99, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0436)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1961 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 99, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0437)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1961 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 99, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0438)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense, 1961 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 99, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0439)
  - Football Parade, Fall 1962
    - Football Parade, Fall 1962; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0440)
  - Southern California, 1962 September 22
    Duke loss, score: 7-14
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0441)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0442)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0443)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0444)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0445)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0446)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: 1 reel with sound, 1962 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 105, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0447)
  - South Carolina, 1962 September 29
    Duke win, score: 21-8
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0448)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0449)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0450)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0451)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0452)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0453)
  - Florida, 1962 October 06
    - Duke vs. Florida: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0454)
    - Duke vs. Florida: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0455)
    - Duke vs. Florida: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0456)
    - Duke vs. Florida: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0457)
  - California, 1962 October 13
    - Duke vs. California: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0458)
    - Duke vs. California: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0459)
    - Duke vs. California: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0460)
    - Duke vs. California: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0461)
    - Duke vs. California: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0462)
    - Duke vs. California: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0463)
  - Clemson, 1962 October 20
    Duke win, score: 16-0
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0464)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0465)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0466)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0467)
  - NC State, 1962 October 27
    Duke win, score: 21-14
    - Duke vs. NC State: 1 of 3, 1962 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0468)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 of 3, 1962 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0469)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 3 of 3, 1962 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0470)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 1 of 2 wide, 1962 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0471)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 of 2 wide, 1962 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0472)
  - Georgia Tech, 1962 November 03
    Duke loss, score: 9-20
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0473)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0474)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0475)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0476)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0477)
  - Maryland, 1962 November 10
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0478)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0479)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0480)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0481)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0482)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0483)
  - Wake Forest, 1962 November 17
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0484)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0485)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0486)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0487)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0488)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 95, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0489)
  - North Carolina, 1962 November 24
    Duke win, score: 16-14
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 1 of 3 regular, 1962 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0490)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 of 3 regular, 1962 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0491)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 3 of 3 regular, 1962 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0492)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 1 of 3 wide, 1962 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0493)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 of 3 wide, 1962 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0494)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 3 of 3 wide, 1962 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0495)
  - South Carolina, 1963 September 21
    Duke win, score: 22-14
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 of 2 regular, 1963 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0496)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 of 2 regular, 1963 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0497)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 of 3 wide, 1963 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0498)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 of 3 wide, 1963 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0499)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 3 of 3 wide, 1963 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 96, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0500)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: wide, 1963 September 21; DVD
  - Virginia, 1963 September 28
    Duke win, score: 30-8
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0501)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0502)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0503)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0504)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 1 of 3 wide, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0505)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 2 of 3 wide, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0506)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 3 of 3 wide, 1963 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0507)
  - Maryland, 1963 October 05
    Duke win, score: 30-12
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 regular, 1963 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0508)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 regular, 1963 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0509)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 regular, 1963 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0510)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 wide, 1963 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0511)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 wide, 1963 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0512)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 wide, 1963 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0513)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: wide, 1963 October 05; DVD
      Master
    - Duke vs. Maryland: wide, 1963 October 05; DVD
  - California, 1963 October 12
    Duke T, score: 22-22
    - Duke vs. California: 1 of 3, 1963 October 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0514)
  - Clemson, 1963 October 19
    Duke win, score: 35-30
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 1 of 3, 1963 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0515)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 of 3, 1963 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0516)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 3 of 3, 1963 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0517)
  - NC State, 1963 October 26
    Duke loss, score: 7-21
    - Duke vs. NC State: 1 regular, 1963 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0518)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 regular, 1963 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0519)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 1 wide, 1963 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0520)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 wide, 1963 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0521)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 3 wide, 1963 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0522)
  - Georgia Tech, 1963 November 02
    Duke loss, score: 6-30
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1, 1963 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0523)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2, 1963 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0524)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1963 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0525)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1963 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0526)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1963 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0527)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1963 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0528)
  - Wake Forest, 1963 November 09
    Duke win, score: 39-7
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0529)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0530)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0531)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0532)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Half wide, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0533)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter wide, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0534)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter wide, 1963 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0535)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: regular and wide, 1963 November 09; DVD
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: regular and wide, 1963 November 09; DVD
  - Navy, 1963 November 16
    Duke loss, score: 25-38
    - Duke vs. Navy: First Quarter regular, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0536)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Second Quarter regular, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0537)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Third Quarter regular, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0538)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Fourth Quarter regular, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0539)
    - Duke vs. Navy: First Quarter wide, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0540)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Second Quarter wide, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0541)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Third Quarter wide, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0542)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Fourth Quarter wide, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0543)
    - Duke vs. Navy: TV Highlights, 1963 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0544)
  - North Carolina, 1963 November 28
    Duke loss, score: 14-16
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter regular, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0545)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter regular, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0546)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter regular, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0547)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter regular, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0548)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter wide, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0549)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter wide, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0550)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter wide, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0551)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter wide, 1963 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 68, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0552)
  - South Carolina, 1964 September 19
    Duke T, score: 9-9
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: First Quarter wide, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0553)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Second Quarter wide, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0554)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Third Quarter wide, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0555)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Fourth Quarter wide, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0556)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: First Quarter regular, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0557)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Second Quarter regular, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0558)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Third Quarter regular, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0559)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Fourth Quarter regular, 1964 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0560)
  - Virginia, 1964 September 26
    Duke win, score: 30-0
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter regular, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0561)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter regular, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0562)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter regular, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0563)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter regular, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0564)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter wide, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0565)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter wide, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0566)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter wide, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0567)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter wide, 1964 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0568)
  - Maryland, 1964 October 10
    Duke win, score: 24-17
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter wide, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0569)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter wide, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0570)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Half wide, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0571)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0572)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0573)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Third Quarter, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0574)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Fourth Quarter, 1964 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0575)
  - NC State, 1964 October 17
    Duke win, score: 35-3
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Half Offense, 1964 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0577)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Half Offense, 1964 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0578)
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Half Defense, 1964 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0579)
  - Army, 1964 October 24
    - Duke vs. Army: First Quarter wide, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0580)
    - Duke vs. Army: Second Quarter wide, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0581)
    - Duke vs. Army: Third Quarter wide, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0582)
    - Duke vs. Army: Fourth Quarter, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0583)
    - Duke vs. Army: First Quarter regular, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0584)
    - Duke vs. Army: Second Quarter regular, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0585)
    - Duke vs. Army: Third Quarter regular, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0586)
    - Duke vs. Army: Fourth Quarter regular, 1964 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0587)
  - Army and Navy Highlights, 1964 October 24 and 1964 November 14
    Duke win against Army, Duke loss against Navy
    - Army and Navy Highlights, 1964 October 24 and 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0576)
  - Georgia Tech, 1964 October 31
    Duke loss, score: 8-21
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 1, 1964 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0588)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 2, 1964 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0589)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1964 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0590)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1964 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0591)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1964 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0592)
  - Wake Forest, 1964 November 07
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0593)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0594)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0595)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0596)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0597)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0598)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 1, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0599)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 2, 1964 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0600)
  - Navy, 1964 November 14
    - Duke vs. Navy: Defense 1, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0601)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Offense 1, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0602)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Defense 2, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0603)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Offense 2, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0604)